Guide to the Irving McNeil Ives papers, 1862-1958
Ives, Irving McNeil papers, 1862-1958
- Series III. SPEECHES
  - Labor Meeting - 6/13/45 - 1945 (Box 188, Folder 37)
  - Speeches and Statements - 1945 (Box 188, Folder 38)
  - Speeches and statements, undated by I.M.I. (made during Assembly career) - [1930-1946] (Box 188, Folder 39)
  - Retirement Announcement - 1946 (Box 188, Folder 40)
  - George Washington - 19-- (Box 188, Folder 41)
  - Speeches and statements, undated, probably by I. M. I - 19-- (Box 188, Folder 42)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] Address by I. M. I?. N. Y. S. Comm. Against Discrimination in Education? (Sept. 23, 1946) - 1946 (Box 236, Folder 1)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 10/21/46 - Rome: annotated speech - 1946 (Box 236, Folder 2)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 1/14/47 - Radio-Buffalo - 1946 (Box 236, Folder 3)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 2/6/47 - 27th Ward Rep. Comm. Buffalo - 1947 (Box 236, Folder 4)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 2/8/47 - Queens Co. - Lincoln Day - Republican responsibility - 1947 (Box 236, Folder 5)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 2/ 9/47 - NYC: "Laws and actions against discrimination" - 1947 (Box 236, Folder 6)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 2/25/47 - Knoxville, Tenn. Repub. Responsibility in 80th Congress - 1947 (Box 236, Folder 7)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 2/26/47 - Statement re Palestine Problem - 1947 (Box 236, Folder 8)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 3/7/47 - Statement by I.M.I. before the U. S. Senate - 1947 (Box 236, Folder 9)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 3/8/47 - Herald Tribune Forum - 1947 (Box 236, Folder 10)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] Dissensions and complexities of Congress - N. Y. - Printer's Assoc.: - 1947 (Box 236, Folder 11)
    New York Employing Printer's Association
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 3/28/47 - Colgate University - 1947 (Box 236, Folder 12)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 4/16/47 - N. Y. Economic Club - Labor Relations from Management Angle - 1947 (Box 236, Folder 13)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 4/29/47 - Greater N. Y. Fund, NYC. - Welfare Message - 1947 (Box 236, Folder 14)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/16/47 - N. J. Bankers, Atlantic City - The State of Our Economy - 1947 (Box 236, Folder 15)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/24/47 - Schroon Lake, N. Y. - N. Y. S. Young Republican Clubs - History of Republican Party - 20-32 - Responsibility Now - 1947 (Box 236, Folder 16)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 6/11/47 - Statement by I.M.I. in S. 984 - re discrimination - 1947 (Box 236, Folder 17)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 9/24/47 - Harlem Div. - Rep. Com. NYC - State Federal FEPC - 1947 (Box 236, Folder 18)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 10/19/47 - New York City - Dedication of Memorial to Heroes of the Battle of Warsaw - 1947 (Box 236, Folder 19)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 11/ 1947 - Radio Statement Release for Senator Chapman Revercomb - 1947 (Box 236, Folder 20)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 11/6/47 - Alfred University - Economic and Labor Management Problem - 1947 (Box 236, Folder 21)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 11/13/47 - Rep. Women of Penna. Harrisburg - Taft-Hartley Act - 1947 (Box 236, Folder 22)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 11/30/47 - Radio - D. C. - The Marshal Plan - 1947 (Box 236, Folder 23)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 12/29/47 - NYC - Testimonial to Dr. Abba Hillel Silver - 1947 (Box 236, Folder 24)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] Misc. Policy Statements, Press Releases and speeches of I.M.I. - 19-- [1947] (Box 236, Folder 25)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 2/ 4/48 - Senate Speech on Seaway - 1948 (Box 236, Folder 26)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 1/31/48 - NYC - Speech to the Albany Society - 1948 (Box 236, Folder 27)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] Labor Relations - 1948 - Original Statement "Remington Rand controversy - Background Data" - 3/16/48 - 1947-1948 (Box 236, Folder 28)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 3/29/48 - Washington, D. C. - Order of AHEPA (American Hellenic Education Progressive Association) - 1948 (Box 236, Folder 29)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/8/48 - Oberlin College (Ohio) - 1948 (Box 236, Folder 30)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 6/14/48 - Excerpts from Congressional Record - Reciprocal Trade Agreements - 1948 (Box 236, Folder 31)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 8/6/48 - Senate - 1948 (Box 236, Folder 32)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 9/12/48 - NYC Comm. for Relief of Italian Orphans - 1948 (Box 236, Folder 33)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 10/ 8/48 - Elmira - N. Y. S. Teachers - 1948 (Box 236, Folder 34)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 10/13/18 - NYC - 1948 (Box 236, Folder 35)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 10/14/48 - Excerpts from Remarks? American Jewish Comm?.NYC - FEPC - 1948 (Box 236, Folder 36)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 10/15/48 - Radio - White Plains, N. Y. - 1948 (Box 236, Folder 37)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 10/27/48 - Radio speech - 1948 (Box 236, Folder 38)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] Speech - Greetings to the New State of Israel - 1948 (Box 236, Folder 39)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] Misc. Speeches and Statements written for/by I.M.I. (sent from Westchester) - 1948-1952, 19-- (Box 236, Folder 40)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 1/ 23/49 - NYC - Freedom House, Freedom Parade - 1949 (Box 236, Folder 41)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 1/25/49 - Statement of I.M.I. at Hearing held before Comm. on Rules and Administration - 1949 (Box 236, Folder 42)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 1/30/49 - Syracuse, N. Y. - Commencement Address at Syracuse University - Political Awareness - 1949 (Box 236, Folder 43)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 2/12/49 - Grand Rapids, Mich. - Keynote Address to Republican Convention - 1949 (Box 236, Folder 44)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 2/22/49 - NYC ?Sons of Revolution address on foreign policy: "Washington's Farewell Address" - 1949 (Box 236, Folder 45)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 3/22/49 - Orig. Reading Copy - Philadelphia, Penna. - 1949 (Box 236, Folder 46)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 4/15/49 - NYC - NBC radio presentation on labor legislation - 1949 (Box 236, Folder 47)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 4/19/49 - Washington, D. C. - 1949 (Box 236, Folder 48)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/1/49 (Sunday) - 158 Anniversary - Polish Constitution - Manhattan Center, NYC - 1949 (Box 236, Folder 49)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/11/49 - Statement in Senate - FEPC Legislation before Comm. - 1949 (Box 236, Folder 50)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/14/49 (Saturday) - 1st Anniversary - State of Israel, Madison Square Garden, NYC - 1949 (Box 236, Folder 51)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/22/49 (Sunday) Jamaica Jewish Center, Jamaica, Long Island - 1949 (Box 236, Folder 52)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/31/49 - Statement re National Health Act - 1949 (Box 236, Folder 53)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/31/49 (Tuesday) - Realistic Liberalism - Commencement New School - NYC - 1949 (Box 236, Folder 54)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 8/22/49 - Statement re D. P. - 1949 (Box 237, Folder 1)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 9/12/49 - Buffalo, New York - State Automobile Dealers/Anti-Fair Deal - 1949 (Box 237, Folder 2)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 9/15/49 - Albany, New York, Introducing John F. Dulles - 1949 (Box 237, Folder 3)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 10/29/49 - Executive Industrial Relations Conf. Hershey, Penna. - Misc. on Labor: congressional bills - S. 1970 and S. 1969 - 81st Congress - 1949 (Box 237, Folder 4)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 11/5/49 - re John Foster Dulles Campaign - NYC - 1949 (Box 237, Folder 5)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 1/8/50 - Buffalo, New York - The Challenge of 1950 - 1949 (Box 237, Folder 6)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 1/18/50 - NYS Agricultural Society - Albany, New York - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 7)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 1/ 23/50 - Rochester, New York - Legislative Outlook for '50 - Radio Broadcast - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 8)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 2/ 3, 6, 8 & 9/50 - I.M.I. - Blueprint for a Better America - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 9)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 2/7/50 - Statement by I.M.I. with respect to statement of Republican Principles and Objectives - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 10)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 2/11-12-13/50 - Lincoln Republicanism, Schenectady, Syracuse, Jamestown - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 11)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 2/24/50 - Individual Responsibility in a Free Society - Herald Tribune Fresh Air Forum - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 12)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 3/21/50 - U. S. Senate - Israel - As An Armament Situation - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 13)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 3/30/50 - U. S. Senate - Bipartisan Foreign Policy - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 14)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] Speeches and Statements by I.M.I. - Fall Campaign - 1950 - 1949-1950 (Box 237, Folder 15)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 4/3/50 - WHAM Rochester, N. Y. - Handicaps to Economy in Gov. - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 16)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 4/14/50 - Labor Relations - Triple Cities - Rotary ?Binghamton, N. Y. - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 17)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 4/26/50 - A Measure of Freedom - Television Broadcast - NYC - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 18)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/11/50 - U. S. Senate - For. Reorg. Plan #12 - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 19)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/13/50 - Israel, State of, 1950 - Speech for delivery on Occasion of Second Anniversary of Israel - Alfange - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 20)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/22/50 - Washington, D. C. - "You are your government" - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 21)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 6/3/50 - Young Republican Convention - Wingdale, N. Y. - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 22)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 6/12/50 - Oneonta, N. Y. - Commencement at Hartwick College - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 23)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 6/15/50 - U. S. Senate - Congressional and Investigating Committees - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 24)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 6/19/50 - Message - Radio - "Congressional Investigations" - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 25)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 7/3/50 - VFW Encampment - Rochester, New York - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 26)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 7/20/50 - Statement re: Korea - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 27)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 7/29/50 - radio interview - War Time Regulations - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 28)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 8/11/50 - U. S. Senate - Defense Production Act of 1950 - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 29)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 8-27-50 - Investigating Commissions - Draft of Article for NY Times - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 30)
  - 1950 [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 9/ 24/50 - NYC - The Challenge of Interfaith - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 31)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 10/1/1950 - Freedom's Responsibility - Carnegie Hall, NYC - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 32)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 11/1/50 - WOR, NYC - Campaign speech - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 33)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 11/7/50 - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 34)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 11/10/50 - Re: Taft-Hartley Law - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 35)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 1/21/51 - Rochester, New York - Foreign policy excerpts - 1951 (Box 237, Folder 36)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 2/12/51 - Lincoln Day Address - Utica, New York - 1951 (Box 237, Folder 37)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 3/4/51 66th Annual meeting HIAS (Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society) - New York City - 1951 (Box 237, Folder 38)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 3/10/51 - Legislative Correspondents' Association - Dinner - Albany: program "Command Incision" or "The Knife Before Christmas" - 1951 (Box 237, Folder 39)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 4/11/51 - Statement - Re: Recall of MacArthur - 1951 (Box 237, Folder 40)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 4/14/51 - It's Not War: It's Not Peace - New York City - 1951 (Box 237, Folder 41)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/6/51 - Third Israel Anniversary - Carnegie Hall - 1951 (Box 237, Folder 42)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/11/51 - NYC (Repub. State Com.) - 1951 (Box 237, Folder 43)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/10/51 - I am an American Day - Buffalo - 1951 (Box 237, Folder 44)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/29/51 - Text of Letter - 1951 (Box 237, Folder 45)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 6/25/51 - Proposed Extension of the Defense Production Act of 1950" - 1951 (Box 237, Folder 46)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 6/29/51 - Senate - Defense Production Act of 1950 - 1951 (Box 237, Folder 47)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 7/22/51 - Colgate Speech - No War - No Peace - 1951 (Box 237, Folder 48)
  - [Speeches.] 8/21/51 - Senate - 1951 (Box 237, Folder 49)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 9/20/51 - 1951 (Box 237, Folder 50)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 9/23/51 - Buffalo Speech - Polish National Alliance - 1951 (Box 237, Folder 51)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 10/29/50 - YMCA Centennial Dinner - New York City - 1951 (Box 237, Folder 52)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 11/1/51 - B'nai B'rith Speech - 1951 (Box 237, Folder 53)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 12/ 12/51 - NYC Insurance Federation Luncheon - 1951 (Box 237, Folder 54)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] Miscellaneous Speeches 1947-1951 - 1947-1951 (Box 237, Folder 55)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] Speeches and Statements by I.M.I. - 1951 (Box 237, Folder 56)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] Lincoln Day Speeches - 1951 - Binghamton, Nyack, New York City - 1952 (Box 237, Folder 57)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 3/13/52 (4/1/52) - Opening of Little Falls Station WLF 4 - 1952 (Box 237, Folder 58)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 3/21/52 - DC - Circus Saints and Sinners - 1952 (Box 237, Folder 59)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 3/23/52 - Everyman's Bible Class - Staten Island - 1952 (Box 237, Folder 60)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 4/2/52 - 1952 (Box 237, Folder 61)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 4/4/52 - Vocational Education - Syracuse - 1952 (Box 237, Folder 62)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 4/5/52 - Federal Employees - Utica - 1952 (Box 237, Folder 63)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 4/14/52 - Richmond Co. - 1952 (Box 237, Folder 64)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 4/18/52 - Industrial Relations Conf. - Buffalo - 1952 (Box 238, Folder 1)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 4/19/52 - Letter Carriers - Buffalo - 1952 (Box 238, Folder 2)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 4/21/52 - Mutual Agents Assn. - Syracuse - 1952 (Box 238, Folder 3)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 4/29/52 - 4th Israel Anniversary Speech - NYC - 1952 (Box 238, Folder 4)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/7/52 - Excerpts from Greetings - Yavne Hebrew Theol. Seminary - 1952 (Box 238, Folder 5)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/8/52 - Republican Dinner - NYC - 1952 (Box 238, Folder 6)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/11/52 - Beth El Hospital Dedication - Brooklyn - 1952 (Box 238, Folder 7)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/23/25 - re Sen. Clayton Lusk - Cortland - 1952 (Box 238, Folder 8)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/24/52 - Young Republican Convention - Averill Park - N. Y. - 1952 (Box 238, Folder 9)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 6/7/52 - Jewish War Veterans Speech - Swan Lake - 1952 (Box 238, Folder 10)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 6/23/52 - Speech - VFW - Troy - 1952 (Box 238, Folder 11)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 8/26/52 - Address at meeting of N. Y. Republican State Committee - Albany, N. Y. - 1952 (Box 238, Folder 12)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 9/29/52 (Monday) - Excerpts - Women's Republican Club Speech - Poughkeepsie, N. Y. - [1952] (Box 238, Folder 13)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 12/13/[52] - DC Gridiron Dinner - 1952 (Box 238, Folder 14)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] (1/15/53) - Westchester Victory Dinner - 1953 (Box 238, Folder 15)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 2/7/53 - Repub. Lincoln Speech - Queens - 1953 (Box 238, Folder 16)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 2/11/53 - Lincoln Day Speech - Albany, N. Y - 1953 (Box 238, Folder 17)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 2/12/53 - Speech - Oneonta - 1953 (Box 238, Folder 18)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 2/17/53 - VFW Dinner - D. C - 1953 (Box 238, Folder 19)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 2/22/53 - Gesoalde Testimonial Dinner - 1953 (Box 238, Folder 20)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 3/5/53 - American Retail Fed. Dinner - 1953 (Box 238, Folder 21)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 3/10/53 - Mc Letter and TripartiteDeclaration - 1953 (Box 238, Folder 22)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 3/20/53 - Speech on Education - NYC - 1953 (Box 238, Folder 23)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 3/22/53 - Speech - Brooklyn - 1953 (Box 238, Folder 24)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/3/53 - Polish Constitution Day - 1953 (Box 238, Folder 25)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/5/53 - Statement re Discrimination in Employment - 1953 (Box 238, Folder 26)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/7/53 - Speech - Republican Dinner - 1953 (Box 238, Folder 27)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/17/53 - Speech - Jack Javits Testimonial - 1953 (Box 238, Folder 28)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 6/4/53 - Address to ILO Conference accepting Presidency of Conference - 1953 (Box 238, Folder 29)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 8/53 - Statement by I.M.I. on Redevelop. of Niagara River - 1953 (Box 238, Folder 30)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 9/6/53 - 5th Division Speech - 1953 (Box 238, Folder 31)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 10/25/53 - N. Y. Bible Soc. - 1953 (Box 238, Folder 32)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 11/13/53 - Ithaca - 1953 (Box 238, Folder 33)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 2/14/54 - Buffalo Speech - 1954 (Box 238, Folder 34)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 2/23/54 - Statement on S. 692 - To prohibit Discrimination in employment? - 1954 (Box 238, Folder 35)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 3/23/54 - re Norwich postmaster - 1954 (Box 238, Folder 36)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 4/18/54 - Norwich YMCA - Excerpt - 1954 (Box 238, Folder 37)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 6/1/54 - Re: Quartermaster Purchasing Agency - 1954 (Box 238, Folder 38)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 6/23/54 - Address on Albany Congress - 1954 (Box 238, Folder 39)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 6/24/54 - Nassau County - Frank A. Gulotta Testimonial - 1954 (Box 238, Folder 40)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] Misc. speeches and statements - 1954 (Box 238, Folder 41)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 1/17/55 - Letter re Oswego anti-aircraft training camp - [1954] (Box 238, Folder 42)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 1/26/55 - I.M.I. and Lehmann Legislation to promote rehabilitation and preservation of historic NYC properties - 1955 (Box 238, Folder 43)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 1/31/55 - Letter re reciprocal trade agreements - 1955 (Box 238, Folder 44)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 2/8/55 - Anniversary Of Yalta Agreement - 1955 (Box 238, Folder 45)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 2/25/55 - Statement on Senate Floor re Estonian Independence - 1955 (Box 238, Folder 46)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 3/8/55 - Statement on Senate Floor re 150th Anniversary of birthday of Thomas Masaryk - 1955 (Box 238, Folder 47)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 4/1/55 - Congressional Record - Summary of Civilian Conservation Corps. - 1955 (Box 238, Folder 48)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 4/14/55 - 1955 (Box 238, Folder 49)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/3/55 - Statement re S. J. 68 - Salk Polio Vaccine - 1955 (Box 238, Folder 50)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/24/55 - Records sustaining Presidential vote of paybill - S. 1 - 1955 (Box 238, Folder 51)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 6/4/55 - Excerpts from articles appearing in New York World Telegram and Sun - 1955 (Box 238, Folder 52)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 10/22/55 - Address - Columbian Republican League, White Plains, New York - 1955 (Box 238, Folder 53)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 10/22/55 and 10/23/55 - Speeches - 1955 (Box 238, Folder 54)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] Statement of I.M.I. before Senate special maritime Training Subcommittee of? 10/27/55 - 1955 (Box 238, Folder 55)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 11/23/55 Statement - 1955 (Box 238, Folder 56)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 12/15/55 - Brooklyn, N. Y. - Bill of Rights Day - 1954 (Box 238, Folder 57)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 1955 - Speeches - 1955 (Box 238, Folder 58)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 1/5/56 - Re surplus funds - 1956 (Box 238, Folder 59)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 1/26/56 - Statement concerning bill re registration and reporting of welfare and pension plans - 1956 (Box 238, Folder 60)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 2/10/56 - Radio Script - NYC - 1956 (Box 238, Folder 61)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 2/11/56 re Pvt. R. A. Hagelberger - 1956 (Box 238, Folder 62)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 3/56 - Radio script - 1956 (Box 238, Folder 63)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 4/56 - Radio Broadcast #3 - Recorded 3/27/56 - 1956 (Box 238, Folder 64)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/56/ - Radio Broadcast - 1956 (Box 238, Folder 65)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 6/20/56 - Address at Yeshiva University - 1956 (Box 238, Folder 66)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 6/23/56 - Statement by I.M.I. re resigning from Senate - 1956 (Box 238, Folder 67)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 7/2/56 - Resolution to establish U. S. Academy of Nursing - 1956 (Box 238, Folder 68)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 7/17/56 - Radio broadcast - 1956 (Box 238, Folder 69)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 10/15/56 - Re marine dependents - 1956 (Box 238, Folder 70)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 10/29/56 - St. George Hotel - Brooklyn - 1956 (Box 238, Folder 71)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 1956 - speeches - 1956 (Box 238, Folder 72)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 1/3/57 - Statement re: Change in Senate Rules - 1957 (Box 238, Folder 73)
  - 1957 [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 1/7/57 - Nominations - Air Force Academy - 1957 (Box 238, Folder 74)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 2/7/57 - Nominations - Merchant Marine Academy - 1957 (Box 238, Folder 75)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 2/14/57 - Statement concerning Civil Rights - 1957 (Box 238, Folder 76)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 4/25/57 - Re. Labor Hearings - 1957 (Box 238, Folder 77)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/4/57 - Program transcript - "Congressional close up" - 1957 (Box 238, Folder 78)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 5/27/57 - Statement re Labor Hearings - 1957 (Box 238, Folder 79)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 6/5/57 - Statement re S. 2175 - 1957 (Box 238, Folder 80)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 6/6/57 - Remarks re Old Age Survivors Insurance Program - NYC - 1957 (Box 238, Folder 81)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 6/7/57 - Press release of correspondence regarding racketeering - 1957 (Box 238, Folder 82)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 6/23/57 - Transcript of TV interview - 1957 (Box 238, Folder 83)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 6/24/57 - Radio Broadcast - 1957 (Box 238, Folder 84)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 6/24/57 - Statement to Special Subcommittee of the Senate Comm. on Rules and Administration, concerning legislation to Amend Rule XXII - 1957 (Box 238, Folder 85)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 6/28/57 - Speech "Why I Am a Republican" - 1957 (Box 238, Folder 86)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 7/14/57 - Transcript of T. V. Interview - 1957 (Box 238, Folder 87)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 7/17/57 - Letter to Senator Chavez from Senators I.M.I. and Javits regarding N. Y. Barge Canal - 1957 (Box 238, Folder 88)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 7/17/57 - Joint Statement on Niagara Power, Senators I.M.I. and Javits - 1957 (Box 238, Folder 89)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 7/18/57 - Statement regarding Improprer activities in labor annd Management - 1957 (Box 238, Folder 90)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 7/25/57 - I.M.I. and Javits - Joint Resolution re 350th Anniversary of exploration of Hudson River - 1957 (Box 238, Folder 91)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 8/1/57 - Housing - lower down payments - 1957 (Box 238, Folder 92)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 8/12/57 - Statement on Senate Floor for Niagara Power Bill - 1957 (Box 238, Folder 93)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 10/3/57 - GE Electronics Park - Syracuse, New York - 1957 (Box 238, Folder 94)
  - [U. S. Senate. Speeches.] 1957 - undated speeches and statements - [1957] (Box 238, Folder 95)